http://www.consumer.gov.au/index.php/privacy

Skip to main content
HomeAboutLegislationYear In ReviewEnforcementConsumer Policy in AustraliaDevelopmentMaintaining consistency with the ACLInternational engagementResourcesPolicy ToolkitConsumersConsumer Questions and ComplaintsACTNationalNew South WalesNorthern TerritoryQueenslandSouth AustraliaTasmaniaVictoriaWestern AustraliaOther Consumer ProtectionsACTNationalNew South WalesNorthern TerritoryQueenslandSouth AustraliaTasmaniaVictoriaWestern AustraliaArticlesResources and guidesAustralian Competition and Consumer CommissionSharing Economy PlatformsFor teachersChanges to the Australian Consumer LawNational ProjectsPrevious projectsConsultations and ReviewsAustralian Consumer Law ReviewTerms of ReferenceIssues PaperInterim ReportFinal ReportProjectsMediaAustralian Consumer SurveyAustralian Consumer Survey 2011Public ConsultationsConsumer Affairs ForumMembersCommuniquésExtranet (for officials)
Privacy
This website is managed by The Treasury. The Treasury is subject to the Privacy Act which requires that the Treasury comply with the Australian Privacy Principles (APPs) as set out in the Privacy Act. The APPs regulate the Treasury’s obligations in relation to the collection, storage, use, disclosure, quality and security of personal information and access and correction rights of individuals in relation to their personal information.
The Treasury’s information handling practices are outlined in its Privacy policy. This document sets out all of the information required by APP1.4 of the Privacy Act and outlines how an individual may seek access or correction to their personal information or make a complaint about how the Treasury has handled their personal information.
